[
    {
        "question": "Which Disney character famously leaves a glass slipper behind at a royal ball?",
        "correctAnswer": "Cinderella",
        "answer1": "Sleeping Beauty",
        "answer2": "Ariel",
        "answer3": "Cinderella",
        "answer4": "Snow White"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are made and repaired by a cobbler?",
        "correctAnswer": "Shoes",
        "answer1": "Shoes",
        "answer2": "Clothes",
        "answer3": "Leather goods",
        "answer4": "Vases"
    },
    {
        "question": "A magnet would most likely attract which of the following?",
        "correctAnswer": "Metal",
        "answer1": "Glass",
        "answer2": "Metal",
        "answer3": "Sand",
        "answer4": "Rubber"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the smallest country in the world?",
        "correctAnswer": "Vatican City",
        "answer1": "San Marino",
        "answer2": "Monaco",
        "answer3": "Vatican City",
        "answer4": "Belau"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the bible, when was Jesus born?",
        "correctAnswer": "24-Dec",
        "answer1": "26-Dec",
        "answer2": "25-Dec",
        "answer3": "18-Dec",
        "answer4": "24-Dec"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who sang the 2014 hit ''Shake it off''?",
        "correctAnswer": "Taylor Swift",
        "answer1": "Taylor Swift",
        "answer2": "Ariana Grande",
        "answer3": "Selena Gomez",
        "answer4": "Rihanna"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is The Sahara?",
        "correctAnswer": "A desert",
        "answer1": "A lake",
        "answer2": "A desert",
        "answer3": "A mountain",
        "answer4": "A river"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is âˆš121?",
        "correctAnswer": "11",
        "answer1": "9",
        "answer2": "10",
        "answer3": "11",
        "answer4": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many colors are in a rainbow?",
        "correctAnswer": "7",
        "answer1": "5",
        "answer2": "6",
        "answer3": "7",
        "answer4": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first president of the United States?",
        "correctAnswer": "George Washington",
        "answer1": "John Adams",
        "answer2": "Thomas Jefferson",
        "answer3": "George Washington",
        "answer4": "Alexander Hamilton"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the most popular eye color in the world?",
        "correctAnswer": "Brown",
        "answer1": "Brown",
        "answer2": "Blue",
        "answer3": "Grey",
        "answer4": "Hazel"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who wrote ''The Lord of The Rings'' trilogy?",
        "correctAnswer": "J.R.R. Tolkien",
        "answer1": "George R.R. Martin",
        "answer2": "J.R.R. Tolkien",
        "answer3": "C.S. Lewis",
        "answer4": "J.K. Rowling"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the University of Cambridge located?",
        "correctAnswer": "England",
        "answer1": "The United States",
        "answer2": "Scotland",
        "answer3": "Ireland",
        "answer4": "England"
    },
    {
        "question": "When did the first moon landing happen?",
        "correctAnswer": "1969",
        "answer1": "1971",
        "answer2": "1959",
        "answer3": "1969",
        "answer4": "1964"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the youngest sister in the Kardashian family?",
        "correctAnswer": "Kylie",
        "answer1": "Kourtney",
        "answer2": "Kim",
        "answer3": "Kylie",
        "answer4": "Kendall"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the singer Lorde from?",
        "correctAnswer": "New Zealand",
        "answer1": "Australia",
        "answer2": "New Zealand",
        "answer3": "The United States",
        "answer4": "The United Kingdom"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these terms is not associated with trigonometry?",
        "correctAnswer": "Lap",
        "answer1": "Lap",
        "answer2": "Sin",
        "answer3": "Cos",
        "answer4": "Tan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a famous K-pop girl group?",
        "correctAnswer": "Fifth Harmony",
        "answer1": "Blackpink",
        "answer2": "Twice",
        "answer3": "Fifth Harmony",
        "answer4": "Aespa"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the world's longest river?",
        "correctAnswer": "The Nile",
        "answer1": "The Mississippi",
        "answer2": "The Nile",
        "answer3": "The Amazon",
        "answer4": "The Yangtze"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which city hosted the summer Olympics in 2012?",
        "correctAnswer": "London",
        "answer1": "Paris",
        "answer2": "Tokyo",
        "answer3": "Wellington",
        "answer4": "London"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the Great Barrier Reef located?",
        "correctAnswer": "Australia",
        "answer1": "New Zealand",
        "answer2": "Australia",
        "answer3": "The United States",
        "answer4": "South Africa"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Greek mythology, who is the God of the sea?",
        "correctAnswer": "Poseidon",
        "answer1": "Zeus",
        "answer2": "Hades",
        "answer3": "Athena",
        "answer4": "Poseidon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Hogwarts house was Harry Potter in?",
        "correctAnswer": "Gryffindor",
        "answer1": "Slythering",
        "answer2": "Hufflepuff",
        "answer3": "Ravenclaw",
        "answer4": "Gryffindor"
    },
    {
        "question": "What sport does Cristiano Ronaldo play?",
        "correctAnswer": "Football",
        "answer1": "Basketball",
        "answer2": "Tennis",
        "answer3": "Football",
        "answer4": "Baseball"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the musical artist who sings the song ''New Rules''?",
        "correctAnswer": "Dua Lipa",
        "answer1": "Selena Gomez",
        "answer2": "Zara Larsson",
        "answer3": "Adele",
        "answer4": "Dua Lipa"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the actor who played Jack in Titanic?",
        "correctAnswer": "Leonardo DiCaprio",
        "answer1": "Leonardo DiCaprio",
        "answer2": "Tom Cruise",
        "answer3": "Ryan Gosling",
        "answer4": "Keanu Reeves"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which ocean is the Bermuda Triangle located?",
        "correctAnswer": "Atlantic Ocean",
        "answer1": "Pacific Ocean",
        "answer2": "Atlantic Ocean",
        "answer3": "Southern Ocean",
        "answer4": "Indian Ocean"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which fictional city is the home of Batman?",
        "correctAnswer": "Gotham city",
        "answer1": "Starr city",
        "answer2": "Starling city",
        "answer3": "Gotham city",
        "answer4": "Central city"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which planet is closest to Earth?",
        "correctAnswer": "Venus",
        "answer1": "Mercury",
        "answer2": "Venus",
        "answer3": "Mars",
        "answer4": "Jupiter"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which boyband is Niall Horan a member of?",
        "correctAnswer": "One direction",
        "answer1": "The Wanted",
        "answer2": "Big time rush",
        "answer3": "One direction",
        "answer4": "Backstreet boys"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which company uses Santa Claus for their advertisements?",
        "correctAnswer": "Coca Cola",
        "answer1": "Pepsi",
        "answer2": "Red Bull ",
        "answer3": "Nike",
        "answer4": "Coca Cola"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which nation's slogan is ''Keep calm and carry on''?",
        "correctAnswer": "Britain",
        "answer1": "Australia",
        "answer2": "Ireland",
        "answer3": "Britain",
        "answer4": "France"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Johnny Depp's character's name in ''Pirates of the Caribbean''?",
        "correctAnswer": "Jack Sparrow",
        "answer1": "Jack Sparrow",
        "answer2": "Will Turner",
        "answer3": "Blackbeard",
        "answer4": "Billy the Kidd"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of One Direction's first official single in 2011?",
        "correctAnswer": "What makes you beautiful ",
        "answer1": "One thing",
        "answer2": "Live while we're young",
        "answer3": "Rock me",
        "answer4": "What makes you beautiful"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the Oval Office located in the White House?",
        "correctAnswer": "The west wing",
        "answer1": "The east wing",
        "answer2": "The west wing",
        "answer3": "The north ",
        "answer4": "The south"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which birds are often associated with delivering babies?",
        "correctAnswer": "Storks",
        "answer1": "Storks",
        "answer2": "Crows",
        "answer3": "Doves",
        "answer4": "Pigeons"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many players are in a baseball team?",
        "correctAnswer": "9",
        "answer1": "11",
        "answer2": "12",
        "answer3": "7",
        "answer4": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country occupies half of South America's western coast",
        "correctAnswer": "Chile",
        "answer1": "Chile",
        "answer2": "Argentina",
        "answer3": "Bolivia",
        "answer4": "Venezuela"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is hummus made from?",
        "correctAnswer": "Chickpeas",
        "answer1": "Corn",
        "answer2": "Chickpeas",
        "answer3": "Potatoes",
        "answer4": "Rye"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the 1993 movie about dinosaurs?",
        "correctAnswer": "Jurassic Park",
        "answer1": "Jurassic Park",
        "answer2": "Jaws",
        "answer3": "The Inglorious Rex",
        "answer4": "Land of the lost"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who wrote horror classic ''It''?",
        "correctAnswer": "Stephen King",
        "answer1": "Clive Barker",
        "answer2": "Stephen King",
        "answer3": "Peter Straub",
        "answer4": "Bram Stoker"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the most spoken language worldwide?",
        "correctAnswer": "Chinese",
        "answer1": "English",
        "answer2": "Spanish",
        "answer3": "French",
        "answer4": "Chinese"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city is known as the City of Love?",
        "correctAnswer": "Paris",
        "answer1": "Madrid",
        "answer2": "Paris",
        "answer3": "Rome",
        "answer4": "Lisbon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is the largest?",
        "correctAnswer": "Alaska",
        "answer1": "Alaska",
        "answer2": "Texas",
        "answer3": "California",
        "answer4": "Montana"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many days are in a leap year?",
        "correctAnswer": "366",
        "answer1": "364",
        "answer2": "365",
        "answer3": "366",
        "answer4": "367"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which astrological sign's symbol is the crab?",
        "correctAnswer": "Cancer",
        "answer1": "Cancer",
        "answer2": "Scorpio",
        "answer3": "Virgo",
        "answer4": "Libra"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which band sings the popular 80s hit ''Every breath you take''?",
        "correctAnswer": "The Police",
        "answer1": "Wham",
        "answer2": "Genesis",
        "answer3": "The Police",
        "answer4": "The Who"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the only French-speaking province in Canada?",
        "correctAnswer": "Quebec",
        "answer1": "Quebec",
        "answer2": "Ontario",
        "answer3": "Alberta",
        "answer4": "British Colombia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which symbol represents St. Patrick's Day",
        "correctAnswer": "Shamrock",
        "answer1": "Irish flag",
        "answer2": "Shamrock",
        "answer3": "Leprechaun",
        "answer4": "Beer"
    },
    {
        "question": "What happened during the years of 1939-1945?",
        "correctAnswer": "World War II",
        "answer1": "Korean War",
        "answer2": "World War I",
        "answer3": "World War II",
        "answer4": "Preparations fot the first moon landing"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many planets are in our solar system?",
        "correctAnswer": "8",
        "answer1": "6",
        "answer2": "7",
        "answer3": "8",
        "answer4": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country do the Olympics originate from?",
        "correctAnswer": "Greece",
        "answer1": "Greece",
        "answer2": "Rome ",
        "answer3": "Spain",
        "answer4": "Portugal"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest ocean on Earth?",
        "correctAnswer": "Pacific ocean",
        "answer1": "Atlantic ocean",
        "answer2": "Pacific ocean",
        "answer3": "Indian ocean",
        "answer4": "Southern ocean"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the tallest building in the world?",
        "correctAnswer": "Burj Khalifa",
        "answer1": "Empire state building",
        "answer2": "Shanghai Tower",
        "answer3": "Burj Khalifa",
        "answer4": "Merdeka 118"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what city is the White House located?",
        "correctAnswer": "Washington DC",
        "answer1": "Washington DC",
        "answer2": "New York City",
        "answer3": "Chicago",
        "answer4": "Nashville"
    },
    {
        "question": "What percentage of Earth is covered in water?",
        "correctAnswer": "0.7",
        "answer1": "0.5",
        "answer2": "0.6",
        "answer3": "0.7",
        "answer4": "0.4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What's the capital of Russia?",
        "correctAnswer": "Moscow",
        "answer1": "Moscow",
        "answer2": "St. Petersburg",
        "answer3": "Volgograd",
        "answer4": "Vladivostok"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why is July 4th a famous day in the U.S.?",
        "correctAnswer": "Independence day",
        "answer1": "Ending of the civil war",
        "answer2": "Independence day",
        "answer3": "George Washington's birthday",
        "answer4": "The day Christopher Columbus reached America"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many legs does a spider have?",
        "correctAnswer": "8",
        "answer1": "6",
        "answer2": "8",
        "answer3": "12",
        "answer4": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the color of an emerald?",
        "correctAnswer": "Green",
        "answer1": "Blue",
        "answer2": "Purple",
        "answer3": "Green",
        "answer4": "Red"
    },
    {
        "question": "What colors are the stars on theÂ American flag?",
        "correctAnswer": "White",
        "answer1": "White",
        "answer2": "Blue",
        "answer3": "Red",
        "answer4": "Gold"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhichÂ oceanÂ is off the California coast?",
        "correctAnswer": "Pacific",
        "answer1": "Southern",
        "answer2": "Pacific",
        "answer3": "Atlantic",
        "answer4": "Indian"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Disney movie is Elsa in?",
        "correctAnswer": "Frozen",
        "answer1": "Cinderella",
        "answer2": "Zootopia",
        "answer3": "Frozen",
        "answer4": "Tangled"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where does Santa Claus live?",
        "correctAnswer": "The north pole",
        "answer1": "The north pole",
        "answer2": "Santaville",
        "answer3": "Whoville",
        "answer4": "Ice land"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to theÂ Dr. SeussÂ book, who stole Christmas?",
        "correctAnswer": "The grinch",
        "answer1": "Lorax",
        "answer2": "Horton",
        "answer3": "The grinch",
        "answer4": "Cat in a hat"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is famous for Hollywood?",
        "correctAnswer": "California",
        "answer1": "California",
        "answer2": "Nevada",
        "answer3": "New Mexico",
        "answer4": "New York"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do caterpillars turn into?",
        "correctAnswer": "Butterflies",
        "answer1": "Flies",
        "answer2": "Butterflies",
        "answer3": "Moths",
        "answer4": "Ladybugs"
    },
    {
        "question": "On which holiday do you go trick-or-treating?",
        "correctAnswer": "Halloween",
        "answer1": "Halloween",
        "answer2": "Christmas",
        "answer3": "St Patrick's day",
        "answer4": "Valentine's day"
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of cat is considered bad luck?",
        "correctAnswer": "Black",
        "answer1": "White",
        "answer2": "Black",
        "answer3": "Grey ",
        "answer4": "Orange"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a brontosaurus?",
        "correctAnswer": "A dinosaur",
        "answer1": "A dinosaur",
        "answer2": "A nasal disease",
        "answer3": "A part of a cell",
        "answer4": "A music genre"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the fastest land animal?",
        "correctAnswer": "Cheetah",
        "answer1": "Tiger",
        "answer2": "Dingo",
        "answer3": "Lion",
        "answer4": "Cheetah"
    },
    {
        "question": "What color are Smurfs?",
        "correctAnswer": "Blue",
        "answer1": "Yellow",
        "answer2": "Green ",
        "answer3": "Blue",
        "answer4": "White"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
        "correctAnswer": "3",
        "answer1": "3",
        "answer2": "4",
        "answer3": "5",
        "answer4": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which planet in our Solar System is known for having a ring?",
        "correctAnswer": "Saturn",
        "answer1": "Jupiter",
        "answer2": "Mars",
        "answer3": "Saturn",
        "answer4": "Mercury"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest mammal in the world?",
        "correctAnswer": "Whale",
        "answer1": "Whale",
        "answer2": "Elephant",
        "answer3": "Giraffe",
        "answer4": "Dolphin"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which capital city of Europe would you find the Eiffel Tower?",
        "correctAnswer": "Paris",
        "answer1": "Madrid",
        "answer2": "London",
        "answer3": "Paris",
        "answer4": "Rome"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is home to the kangaroo?",
        "correctAnswer": "Australia",
        "answer1": "Egypt",
        "answer2": "Australia",
        "answer3": "Congo",
        "answer4": "Mongolia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is the tallest in the world?",
        "correctAnswer": "Giraffe",
        "answer1": "Giraffe",
        "answer2": "Camel",
        "answer3": "Whale",
        "answer4": "Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country did Justin Bieber come from?",
        "correctAnswer": "Canada",
        "answer1": "The UK",
        "answer2": "USA",
        "answer3": "Australia",
        "answer4": "Canada"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Batman's Butler?",
        "correctAnswer": "Alfred",
        "answer1": "James",
        "answer2": "Alfred",
        "answer3": "Leonard",
        "answer4": "Thomas"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who wielded a sword named Excalibur?",
        "correctAnswer": "King Arthur",
        "answer1": "Merlin",
        "answer2": "Lancelot",
        "answer3": "Gawain",
        "answer4": "Galahad"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do plants produce through photosynthesis?",
        "correctAnswer": "Oxygen",
        "answer1": "Hydrogen",
        "answer2": "Oxygen",
        "answer3": "Lithium",
        "answer4": "Nitrogen"
    },
    {
        "question": "What's the first of Elizabeth Kubler-Ross' Five Stages of Grief?",
        "correctAnswer": "Denial",
        "answer1": "Anger",
        "answer2": "Sadness",
        "answer3": "Denial",
        "answer4": "Depression"
    },
    {
        "question": "When is Cinderella required to leave the ball?",
        "correctAnswer": "By midnight",
        "answer1": "By sunset",
        "answer2": "By sunrise",
        "answer3": "By dusk",
        "answer4": "By midnight"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many different railroads can be bought in the game of Monopoly?",
        "correctAnswer": "4",
        "answer1": "3",
        "answer2": "2",
        "answer3": "4",
        "answer4": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the cup used by Christ at the last supper?",
        "correctAnswer": "The holy grail",
        "answer1": "The holy grail",
        "answer2": "The holy cup",
        "answer3": "The holy glass",
        "answer4": "The holy beaker"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of birds are the stars of the 2006 animated film \"Happy Feet\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Penguins",
        "answer1": "Ducks",
        "answer2": "Ostriches",
        "answer3": "Emus",
        "answer4": "Penguins"
    },
    {
        "question": "What sport is Pele associated with?",
        "correctAnswer": "Soccer",
        "answer1": "Soccer",
        "answer2": "Basketball",
        "answer3": "Rugby",
        "answer4": "Swimming"
    },
    {
        "question": "What ocean separates North America from Europe?",
        "correctAnswer": "Atlantic",
        "answer1": "Pacific",
        "answer2": "Indian",
        "answer3": "Atlantic",
        "answer4": "Southern"
    },
    {
        "question": "What organization in the Harry Potter series is named after Dumbledore's patronus?",
        "correctAnswer": "Order of the Phoenix",
        "answer1": "Order of the Phoenix",
        "answer2": "Azkaban",
        "answer3": "Ministry of Magic",
        "answer4": "Dementors"
    },
    {
        "question": "What popular holiday beverage contains sugar, milk and eggs?",
        "correctAnswer": "Eggnog",
        "answer1": "Butter beer",
        "answer2": "Eggnog",
        "answer3": "Mead",
        "answer4": "Mulled wine"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"The Little Glass Slipper\" is another name for which popular folk tale?",
        "correctAnswer": "Cinderella",
        "answer1": "Snow White",
        "answer2": "Beauty and The Beast",
        "answer3": "Sleeping Beauty",
        "answer4": "Cinderella"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Brazil?",
        "correctAnswer": "Brasila ",
        "answer1": "Rio de Janeiro",
        "answer2": "Sao Paulo",
        "answer3": "Brasila",
        "answer4": "Salvador"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which city would you find Red Square?",
        "correctAnswer": "Moscow",
        "answer1": "Beijing",
        "answer2": "Moscow",
        "answer3": "Pyongyang",
        "answer4": "Bratislava"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a baby kangaroo called?",
        "correctAnswer": "Joey",
        "answer1": "Joey ",
        "answer2": "Rhu",
        "answer3": "Hoppy",
        "answer4": "Cody"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the driest continent?",
        "correctAnswer": "Antarctica",
        "answer1": "Africa",
        "answer2": "Antarctica",
        "answer3": "Oceania",
        "answer4": "South America"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Italian city is the namesake of a pasta dish with meat sauce?",
        "correctAnswer": "Bologna",
        "answer1": "Bologna",
        "answer2": "Napels",
        "answer3": "Turin",
        "answer4": "Palermo"
    },
    {
        "question": "What sign of the zodiac is the first air sign of the calender year?",
        "correctAnswer": "Aquarius ",
        "answer1": "Gemini",
        "answer2": "Aquarius",
        "answer3": "Libra",
        "answer4": "Aries"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which ocean does Bangladesh have direct access to?",
        "correctAnswer": "Indian ocean",
        "answer1": "Atlantic ocean",
        "answer2": "Pacific ocean",
        "answer3": "Indian ocean",
        "answer4": "Southern ocean"
    },
    {
        "question": "What dam was built during the 1930s, creating Lake Mead?",
        "correctAnswer": "Hoover Dam",
        "answer1": "Hoover Dam",
        "answer2": "Three Gorges Dam",
        "answer3": "The Karun-3 Dam",
        "answer4": "The Inguri Dam"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US city is serviced by O'Hare International Airport?",
        "correctAnswer": "Chicago",
        "answer1": "Austin",
        "answer2": "Chicago",
        "answer3": "Washington DC",
        "answer4": "Portland"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the number system using only the symbols 1 and 0?",
        "correctAnswer": "Binary system",
        "answer1": "Dual system",
        "answer2": "Binary system",
        "answer3": "Semi system",
        "answer4": "Sum system"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is an organism called that lives on or in a host animal?",
        "correctAnswer": "Parasite",
        "answer1": "Virus",
        "answer2": "Symbiot",
        "answer3": "Parasite",
        "answer4": "Maximat"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which archipelago is known in Spanish as Islas Malvinas?",
        "correctAnswer": "Falkland Islands",
        "answer1": "South Georgia Island",
        "answer2": "Falkland Islands",
        "answer3": "Faroe Islands",
        "answer4": "Gibraltar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Edam cheese comes from what country?",
        "correctAnswer": "The Netherlands",
        "answer1": "The Netherlands",
        "answer2": "Switzerland",
        "answer3": "Belgium",
        "answer4": "France"
    },
    {
        "question": "What flowers did van Gogh paint most regularly?",
        "correctAnswer": "Sunflowers",
        "answer1": "Roses",
        "answer2": "Sunflowers",
        "answer3": "Tulips",
        "answer4": "Daisies"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which author and philosopher is known for his works The Plague, The Outsider and The Fall?",
        "correctAnswer": "Albert Camus",
        "answer1": "Albert Camus",
        "answer2": "Sigmund Freud",
        "answer3": "Friedrich Nietzsche",
        "answer4": "Arthur Schopenhauer"
    },
    {
        "question": "What nickname was given to baseball hall-of-famer Honus Wagner?",
        "correctAnswer": "Flying Dutchman",
        "answer1": "Blackbeard",
        "answer2": "Flying Dutchman",
        "answer3": "Mayflower",
        "answer4": "Wildman"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who directed the Indiana Jones movies released in the 1980s?",
        "correctAnswer": "Steven Spielberg",
        "answer1": "George Lucas",
        "answer2": "Ridley Scott",
        "answer3": "Steven Spielberg",
        "answer4": "David Lynch"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is eaten traditionally in the UK the day before Ash Wednesday?",
        "correctAnswer": "Pancakes",
        "answer1": "Pancakes",
        "answer2": "Waffles",
        "answer3": "Churros",
        "answer4": "Muffins"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 2000 in Roman Numerals?",
        "correctAnswer": "MM",
        "answer1": "XX",
        "answer2": "LL",
        "answer3": "RR",
        "answer4": "MM"
    },
    {
        "question": "What fruits are fermented to make Perry?",
        "correctAnswer": "Pears",
        "answer1": "Apples",
        "answer2": "Pears",
        "answer3": "Mangos",
        "answer4": "Oranges"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many plates comprise the surface of the Earth?",
        "correctAnswer": "Seven",
        "answer1": "Seven",
        "answer2": "Six",
        "answer3": "Five",
        "answer4": "Eight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country borders Sweden only by bridge?",
        "correctAnswer": "Denmark",
        "answer1": "Norway",
        "answer2": "Estonia",
        "answer3": "Iceland",
        "answer4": "Denmark"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many South American Countries does the equator pass through?",
        "correctAnswer": "3",
        "answer1": "4",
        "answer2": "5",
        "answer3": "2",
        "answer4": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "In 1908, what three letters became recognized as the universal distress signal?",
        "correctAnswer": "SOS",
        "answer1": "MIA",
        "answer2": "HLP",
        "answer3": "SOS",
        "answer4": "AID"
    },
    {
        "question": "What American beer has been long promoted as the \"King of Beers\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Budweiser",
        "answer1": "Budweiser",
        "answer2": "Corona",
        "answer3": "Coors Light",
        "answer4": "Bud Light"
    },
    {
        "question": "On the first of November, Spain celebrates \"Todos los Santos\" which translates to what in English?",
        "correctAnswer": "All Saints Day",
        "answer1": "Labor day",
        "answer2": "All Saints Day",
        "answer3": "Epiphany",
        "answer4": "Day of the Dead"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the United Kingdom European Union membership referendum of 2016, more widely known as?",
        "correctAnswer": "Brexit",
        "answer1": "E-parture",
        "answer2": "Britout",
        "answer3": "Brexit",
        "answer4": "Exit form"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of these is NOT a Korean entertainment company",
        "correctAnswer": "ABC entertainment",
        "answer1": "YG entertainment",
        "answer2": "JYP entertainment",
        "answer3": "SM entertainment",
        "answer4": "ABC entertainment"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many Golden Globe awards has Cate Blanchett won?",
        "correctAnswer": "3",
        "answer1": "0",
        "answer2": "1",
        "answer3": "2",
        "answer4": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is on the Porche logo?",
        "correctAnswer": "Horse",
        "answer1": "Horse",
        "answer2": "Camel",
        "answer3": "Lion",
        "answer4": "Tiger"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the SI Unit for pressure?",
        "correctAnswer": "Pascal",
        "answer1": "Katal",
        "answer2": "Pascal",
        "answer3": "Ohm",
        "answer4": "Volt"
    },
    {
        "question": "What rare Earth element is the second most abundant one in the known Universe?",
        "correctAnswer": "Helium",
        "answer1": "Helium",
        "answer2": "Lithium",
        "answer3": "Hydrogen",
        "answer4": "Carbon"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Asteroid Belt can be found between which two planets?",
        "correctAnswer": "Mars & Jupiter",
        "answer1": "Jupiter & Saturn",
        "answer2": "Earth & Mars",
        "answer3": "Mars & Jupiter",
        "answer4": "Uranus & Neptune"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which astronomical body is 3.67 billion miles from the sun?",
        "correctAnswer": "Pluto",
        "answer1": "Neptune",
        "answer2": "Pluto",
        "answer3": "Jupiter",
        "answer4": "Saturn"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Russian Mensheviks were opposed to what other faction?",
        "correctAnswer": "Bolsheviks",
        "answer1": "Left opposition",
        "answer2": "Constitutional Democratic Party",
        "answer3": "Bolsheviks",
        "answer4": "Socialist Revolutionary Party"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who recorded the song \"Tango in the Night\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Fleetwood Mac",
        "answer1": "Eagles",
        "answer2": "Fleetwood Mac",
        "answer3": "Pink Floyd",
        "answer4": "Led Zeppelin"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Greek mythology, what is the name of the god of Dreams?",
        "correctAnswer": "Morpheus",
        "answer1": "Hermes",
        "answer2": "Hades",
        "answer3": "Morpheus",
        "answer4": "Cassandra"
    },
    {
        "question": "Peter the Great is considered the founding father of what country?",
        "correctAnswer": "Russia",
        "answer1": "Sweden",
        "answer2": "Denmark",
        "answer3": "Austria",
        "answer4": "Russia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What 2003 Samuel L. Jackson\/Colin Farrell movie was based on a mid-1970's TV show?",
        "correctAnswer": "SWAT",
        "answer1": "NYPD Blue",
        "answer2": "Bad Boys",
        "answer3": "SWAT",
        "answer4": "SEAL Team"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the atomic number of tin?",
        "correctAnswer": "50",
        "answer1": "45",
        "answer2": "37",
        "answer3": "61",
        "answer4": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who provided the original voice for Aladdin's Genie?",
        "correctAnswer": "Robin Williams",
        "answer1": "Eddie Murphy",
        "answer2": "Chris Rock",
        "answer3": "Robin Williams",
        "answer4": "Will Smith"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the country that borders Spain immediately to the its west?",
        "correctAnswer": "Portugal",
        "answer1": "Andorra",
        "answer2": "Portugal",
        "answer3": "France",
        "answer4": "Italy"
    },
    {
        "question": "An imperial fathom has how many yards?",
        "correctAnswer": "2",
        "answer1": "1",
        "answer2": "3",
        "answer3": "4",
        "answer4": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What fiber-producing plant is attacked by the boll weevil?",
        "correctAnswer": "Cotton",
        "answer1": "Bamboo",
        "answer2": "Coir",
        "answer3": "Cotton",
        "answer4": "Hemp"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the smallest biological unit of a living organism?",
        "correctAnswer": "Cell",
        "answer1": "Protein",
        "answer2": "Cell",
        "answer3": "DNA",
        "answer4": "RNA"
    },
    {
        "question": "Germany's World War I allies were Austria-Hungary, Bulgaria, and which empire?",
        "correctAnswer": "Ottoman Empire",
        "answer1": "Persian Empire",
        "answer2": "Spanish Empire",
        "answer3": "Ottoman Empire",
        "answer4": "Russian Empire"
    },
    {
        "question": "Riyadh is the capital of what Middle-Eastern country?",
        "correctAnswer": "Saudi Arabia",
        "answer1": "Qatar",
        "answer2": "Jordan ",
        "answer3": "Oman",
        "answer4": "Saudi Arabia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What large African island nation is located just west of Mauritius?",
        "correctAnswer": "Madagascar",
        "answer1": "Trinidad and Tobago",
        "answer2": "Madagascar",
        "answer3": "East Timor",
        "answer4": "Bahrain"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many players are there in a standard baseball team?",
        "correctAnswer": "9",
        "answer1": "10",
        "answer2": "7",
        "answer3": "11",
        "answer4": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What two girls do Archie and Reggie run around with?",
        "correctAnswer": "Betty and Veronica",
        "answer1": "Ethel and Veronica",
        "answer2": "Betty and Josie",
        "answer3": "Veronica and Alice",
        "answer4": "Betty and Veronica"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the second largest country in South America?",
        "correctAnswer": "Argentina",
        "answer1": "Argentina",
        "answer2": "Brazil",
        "answer3": "Colombia",
        "answer4": "Venezuela"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US Navy rank is indicated by three equal stripes?",
        "correctAnswer": "Commander",
        "answer1": "LieutenantÂ ",
        "answer2": "Captain",
        "answer3": "Commander",
        "answer4": "Admiral"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of the US state of Florida?",
        "correctAnswer": "Tallahassee",
        "answer1": "Miami",
        "answer2": "Tallahassee",
        "answer3": "Orlando",
        "answer4": "Tampa"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US city is home to the Field Museum of Natural History?",
        "correctAnswer": "Chicago",
        "answer1": "New York",
        "answer2": "Seattle",
        "answer3": "Chicago",
        "answer4": "Dallas"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which player scored the fastest hat-trick in the Premier League?",
        "correctAnswer": "Sadio Mane",
        "answer1": "Mo Salah",
        "answer2": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "answer3": "Alan Sheerer",
        "answer4": "Sadio Mane"
    },
    {
        "question": "When was the inaugural Premier League season?",
        "correctAnswer": "1992-93",
        "answer1": "2002-03",
        "answer2": "2007-08",
        "answer3": "1995-96",
        "answer4": "1988-89"
    },
    {
        "question": "With 202Â clean sheets, which goalkeeper has the best record in the Premier League?",
        "correctAnswer": "Petr Cech",
        "answer1": "Iker Casillas",
        "answer2": "Gianluigi Buffon",
        "answer3": "Petr Cech",
        "answer4": "Manuel Neuer"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country has won the most World Cups?",
        "correctAnswer": "Brazil",
        "answer1": "Germany",
        "answer2": "Brazil",
        "answer3": "Uruguay",
        "answer4": "England"
    }
]
